Summer is a great time of year – but, unfortunately, it's not just us humans that enjoy it.
夏天是一年中美好的时光——但遗憾的是，享受它的不只是我们人类。
Mosquitos seem to make the most out of the season by biting us, and as well as being annoying, mosquito-borne diseases can be dangerous.
蚊子似乎通过叮咬我们来充分利用这个季节，而且蚊媒疾病不仅令人讨厌，还可能很危险。
What can we do to avoid getting bitten?
我们能做些什么来避免被叮咬呢？
The most obvious answer is to use mosquito repellent.
最明显的答案是使用驱蚊剂。
Professor James Logan from the London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine explains that DEET, the chemical used in many repellents, confuses the insects' sense of smell, making it difficult to recognise humans.
伦敦卫生与热带医学院的詹姆斯·洛根教授解释说，许多驱蚊剂中使用的化学物质DEET会混淆蚊子的嗅觉，使其难以识别人类。
Though be careful – as biologist Roger Eritja points out – any bits of skin that aren't covered by repellent are still likely to get bitten.
不过要小心——正如生物学家罗杰·埃里特哈指出的那样——任何没有被驱蚊剂覆盖的皮肤仍然可能被叮咬。
Logan also recommends using plug-in insecticides to kill or repel mosquitos in the room.
洛根还建议使用插电式杀虫剂来杀死或驱赶房间里的蚊子。
However, it might be best to avoid using electric bug zappers.
然而，最好避免使用电子灭虫器。
Daniel Markowski from the American Mosquito Control Association highlights that mosquitos are only a small proportion of the number of insects they kill, and that many of the others are beneficial.
美国蚊子控制协会的丹尼尔·马科夫斯基强调，蚊子只占它们杀死昆虫数量的一小部分，而许多其他昆虫是有益的。
Clothing is another consideration that affects whether mosquitos choose to attack us.
衣物是影响蚊子是否选择攻击我们的另一个考虑因素。
Amy Glover, writing in the Huffington Post, tells us that dark colours attract mosquitos.
埃米·格洛弗在《赫芬顿邮报》上撰文告诉我们，深色吸引蚊子。
James Logan adds that loose clothing is preferable as it is harder for mosquitos to bite through – they're even able to penetrate jeans if they are worn tightly.
詹姆斯·洛根补充说，宽松的衣服更好，因为蚊子更难叮透——蚊子甚至能穿透牛仔裤，如果穿得很紧的话。
Light, loose clothing also means people sweat less.
浅色、宽松的衣服也意味着人们出汗更少。
A 2019 study showed that mosquitos are able to use the smell of human sweat to find their victims.
2019年的一项研究表明，蚊子能够利用人类汗液的气味来找到它们的受害者。
This is why Homes editor Katie Mortram recommends taking a shower before bed to avoid getting bitten.
这就是为什么《家居》编辑凯蒂·莫特拉姆建议睡前洗澡以避免被叮咬。
Another way to stop the smell of your sweat attracting mosquitos is to use deodorant to disguise the smell of your sweat.
另一种阻止汗味吸引蚊子的方法是使用除臭剂来掩盖汗味。
Masie Vollans – a researcher into mosquito ecology, points out that a compound found in deodorants has been shown to stop mosquitos landing on the skin.
蚊子生态学研究员梅西·沃兰斯指出，除臭剂中发现的一种化合物已被证明能阻止蚊子落在皮肤上。
What we eat and drink may also have an impact on how attractive we are to mosquitos.
我们的饮食也可能影响我们对蚊子的吸引力。
Vollans mentions two studies that found drinking beer and eating bananas can make people more attractive to mosquitos.
沃兰斯提到两项研究发现，喝啤酒和吃香蕉会使人们对蚊子更有吸引力。
So, as well as using repellents and insecticides, thinking about our clothing, reducing our sweat and changing what we eat and drink could help to reduce the risk of mosquito bites.
所以，除了使用驱虫剂和杀虫剂，考虑我们的穿着、减少出汗以及改变饮食，都有助于降低被蚊子叮咬的风险。